翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
The key language feature that we're going to use
我们将使用关键的语言特性
to make it more natural to represent the entire universe of dogs or whatever else,
来更自然地模拟狗这个概念
is that classes in Java can contain not just functions,
Java 中的类不仅可以包含函数
but also data.
还可以包含数据
So what I mean by that is that we are going to augment our Dog class so that dogs have properties, like size.
我们将增强 Dog 类让狗具有大小之类的属性
And that class is going to serve as the blueprint for all dogs out there.
这个类将成为所有狗的模板
And then we're going to instantiate that class into specific objects that we can then manipulate.
然后把这个类实例化成可操作的特定对象
Now, that will make more sense once we actually try out an example.
举个例子能说得更清楚
So let's jump right in.
我们看一下
So hopefully, you've seen something pretty much like this.
你们也许见过类似的东西
Now, I know some of the people taking this class are coming from a MATLAB only background.
有些人可能会一点 MATLAB
I have a little example here that you can read to get a sense of what this is all about.
可以读一读这个小例子
But let's try it out in Java and see what it's like to make a dog blueprint.
但现在我们在 Java 中试一下，看看怎么制作狗的模板
So what I'm going to do, I'll reopen my Dog class.
重新打开 Dog 类
And I'm going to say a dog is not just a noise-making machine.
狗不仅仅会制造噪音
Actually, a dog also has a property.
狗还有其他属性
That property is a dog is going to have, let's say, a weightInPounds.
比方说体重
So as an American, I use the bizarre pounds system as opposed to kilograms.
作为一个美国人，我不太使用千克，而是奇怪的磅
We're just going to roll with it.
不用纠结它
And that specifies how big a dog is.
这个属性规定了狗有多大
Then what I'm going to do is, I'm going to change the MakeNoise method.
然后改变 makeNoise 方法
And it's going to have a few cases.
有这样几种情况
So if the weight in pounds of a dog is less than say 10,
如果狗的体重小于10磅
we're going to say it's going to yip.
它会发出“yip”的声音
Otherwise if the weight in pounds less than 30,
否则，如果狗的体重小于30磅
then we will say that it barks.
它会发出“bark”的声音
Otherwise it's such a large dog, that it has a woof sound.
否则它就是一只很大的狗，会发出“woof”的声音
So there's no Malamutes here, like that dog that we had a beautiful ow-ooh.
这里没有能发出“ow-ooh”叫声的阿拉斯加犬
So we'll default to woof for large dogs.
所以大型犬默认使用“woof”
So that's the makeNoise method.
那么 makeNoise 方法改好了
And now if we try and compile our Dog class,
现在编译 Dog 类
I get this funny message.
会有一条奇怪的信息
Non-static variable weightInPounds cannot be referenced from a static context.
非静态变量 weightInPounds 不能在静态上下文中引用
So we'll get a better sense of what that means,
之后我会告诉你这是什么意思
but I'm going to tell you that the simple solution for us right now--
但现在简单的解决一下
this is not only the right solution when we get this compiler message--
这不是报错的唯一解决方式
but what I'm going to do here is just delete the word static and pick apart why that is soon.
删掉 static 这个词，稍等会解释原因
Now if I try to compile it, Dog.java compiles.
先就可以编译 Dog.java 了
And this is now a blueprint for all dogs.
这是所有狗的模板
It can have different behavior based on the weightInPounds of the dog.
它能根据狗的 weightInPounds 属性进行不同的行为
And it's just a glorious thing.
这只是一件值得骄傲的事
So let's go into dogLauncher and see what things are like.
我们到 DogLauncher 中看一下
So we now try to compile dogLauncher,
编译 DogLauncher
we get non-static method makeNoise cannot be referenced from a static context.
报错“非静态方法 makeNoise 不能在静态上下文中引用”
So we might be tempted to delete the word static.
我们可能想删掉 static 这个词
That is not the right answer here.
这是不对的
What we want to do instead-- and this is going to be a new piece of syntax--
我们来写下一段新的语法
I'm going to say I need a specific dog.
我需要一条具体的狗
So I'm going to say this is totally new syntax--
这是一个全新的语法
Dog d equals new Dog.
Dog d = new Dog()
This means create a dog, a new dog.
这意味着创造一条新的狗
And let's call that dog in this case d.
并起名为 d
Then what I'm going to do is say d.weightInPounds equals let's say 25.
然后写 d.weightInPounds = 25
So the dog now gains a certain weight.
狗得到了一个体重
And then instead of saying Dog not makeNoise,
狗并非不能制造噪音
I'm going to d makeNoise.
需要写成 d.makeNoise()
That's a really important point.
这点非常重要
So this is like saying great sky dog, the plutonic ideal of all dogs, please make a noise.
原先这样写就像在说：“狗狗们，叫出来吧”
But if we look at the Dog class, this is expecting a specific dog to be making noise.
但观察 Dog 类，它是希望具体某只狗制造噪音
It's saying, if my weight, if me-- me, my, or whoever, yapster--
如果我的体重...emm不管是谁的体重
if my weight in pounds is less than 10, I'm going to do this and so forth.
如果我的体重小于10磅，我会这样做
So instead, what I need to do is reference a specific dog.
所以我们需要引用的是一条特定的狗
In fact in this case, it's the one I just made.
就像我刚刚修改的这样
So if I do javac DogLauncher.java
使用 javac DogLauncher.java 编译
and then do java DogLauncher, I get bark,
然后执行 java DogLauncher，得到 bark
because it's a 25 pound dog.
因为这条狗25磅
If I do 51, and I recompile and run it, then I get woof.
假如是51磅，重新编译运行，得到 woof
So what this piece of code does is it creates a dog,
这段代码创造了一条狗
sets its weight, and then makes that specific dog make noise.
设置体重，让它发出特定的叫声
And we'll be picking more carefully what static means apart in a minute,
稍后会更详细地分析 static 的意义
but I just want to make sure this syntax is clear for now.
但现在只需确保这个语法是正确的
So what I'm going to do is one last little tweak to this Dog class and DogLauncher class
对 Dog 类和 DogLauncher 类做最后一个小调整
before I move on and kind of reflect on what we've done.
之后再来反思我们的做法
So for those of you with some object-oriented programming experience, which is hopefully almost everybody,
对于有面向对象编程经验的人来说，希望人人都有这样的经验
you're probably used to the idea that setting variables like this manually is kind of strange.
你可能会觉得手动设置变量有些奇怪
So more typically what we'll do is the DogLauncher class,
更准确地说我们要修改一下 DogLauncher
when we create the Dog, we'll actually give it as a parameter to the Dog Creation process.
我们一般会在创建 Dog 的同时设置参数
So I'm going to get rid of this.
把这行删掉
And so in order to enable this--
为了实现这一点
I mean if I try right now, it's not going to work.
我先试一下，应该跑不通
It's going to say constructor class and Dog cannot be applied to given types.
报错“Dog 类的构造函数无法应用于给定的类型”
So what it's saying is, I don't know what to do with this number.
意思就是它不知道怎么处理这个数字
So to fix that, what we're going to do is create a special thing, kind of like a method, known as a constructor.
我们要创造一个特殊的东西来解决这个问题，是一个称为构造函数的方法
So I'm just going to say public Dog int w.
这样写 public Dog(int w)
And this is the constructor for we'll call it the One integer constructor for Dogs.
这就是 Dog 的单整数构造函数
So what that's going to do is if I say new Dog and give an integer, this constructor will get called.
如果 new Dog() 时赋予一个整数，就会调用构造函数
And that will specify how the dog is created.
这将指定狗是如何被创造出来的
So in this case, the constructor is kind of trivial.
这种情况下构造函数好像可有可无
The weightInPounds should just be set equal to w.
weightInPound 应该设置成 w
And so now if I try running DogLauncher,
如果现在运行 DogLauncher
I run it and I get woof.
就会得到 woof
So this code is now functioning, because now I've added this constructor.
这段代码没问题了，因为我添加了构造函数
If you came from a language like Python,
如果你使用过 Python 这样的语言
this is very similar to the init method that classes have.
这和类的 init 方法非常类似
One little side note I'll make is,
我要提一点
you'll notice I didn't recompile the Dog class.
你会注意到我没有重新编译 Dog 类
It turns out that the javac command in Java is very smart.
其实 Java 的 javac 命令非常聪明
And if you make a change to Dog and recompile DogLauncher,
如果修改了 Dog 并重新编译 DogLauncher
it will realize there's a dependency.
它会发现其中的依赖关系
DogLauncher needs Dog to work.
DogLauncher 需要 Dog 才能运行
And it'll actually also recompile Dog under that.
所以会重新编译 Dog 类
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）